(
"ai_sub_version": "3.6.0",
"generated_at": "2026-10-09T23:40:12.519514",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"service_tier": null,
"service_tier_subtitles": null,
"service_tier_lyrics": null,
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
青い 水平線を
The blue horizon...
いま駆け抜けてく
...I'm running through it now.
とぎすまされた
With my senses sharpened,
時の流れ
...feeling the flow of time...
感じておくれ
...please feel it.
ときめきへと
Towards the excitement,
動き出す世界は
the world begins to move.
忘れかけてた
A long-forgotten...
遠い夢の
...distant dream...
訪れ
...arrives.
RIDE ON TIME
さまよう想いなら
If your thoughts are wandering,
やさしく受け止めて
gently catch them,
そっと包んで
and softly wrap them up.
Oh, RIDE ON TIME
心に火を点けて
Ignite a fire in your heart,
あふれる喜び
and let the overflowing joy...
広がれ RIDE ON TIME
...spread far and wide! Ride on time!
僕の
My...
輝く未来
...bright future...
さあ、回り始めて
...has finally started to spin.
うつろな日々も 全て
Even the empty days...
愛に 溶け込む
...will all melt into love.
何という朝
What a morning!
今すぐ君のもと
Right now, to where you are,
届けに行こう
I'll go to deliver it.
燃える 心
My burning heart,
迷わず
without any hesitation.
RIDE ON TIME
時よ走り出せ
Time, start running!
愛よ光り出せ
Love, start shining!
目もくらむ程
So bright that it's blinding!
Oh, RIDE ON TIME
心に火を点けて
Ignite a fire in your heart,
飛び立つ魂に
and send it out...
送るよ RIDE ON TIME
...to your soaring soul! Ride on time!
届けに行こう
I'll go to deliver it.
燃える 心
My burning heart...
今こそ
...especially now!
Oh, RIDE ON TIME
時よ走り出せ
Time, start running!
愛よ光り出せ
Love, start shining!
目もくらむ程
So bright that it's blinding!
Oh, ride on time
心に火をつけて
Ignite my heart
飛び立つ魂に
Onto the soaring soul
送るよ Ride on time
I'll send it, ride on time
Oh, oh, oh, ride on time
さまよう想いなら
If they are wandering thoughts,
やさしく受け止めて
gently embrace them,
そっと包んで
and softly wrap them up.
Oh, ride on time 心に火をつけて
Oh, ride on time, ignite my heart
あふれる喜びに 広がれ Ride on time
Let it spread into overflowing joy, ride on time
Oh, ride on time ときを走りだせ
Oh, ride on time, start running through time
愛よ光りだせ 目も眩むほど
Let love shine so bright it dazzles the eyes
Oh, ride on time 心に火をつけて
Oh, ride on time, ignite my heart
飛び立つ魂に 送るよ Ride on time
Onto the soaring soul, I'll send it, ride on time
Hello, hello, it's Gura, hello guys!
水面に映る自分がいた
There was my reflection on the water's surface
「はあ、私は悪いサメです」
"Sigh, I'm a bad shark"
ずっと恐れていた
I was always afraid...
赤く光るその目
...of those red glowing eyes
海の底 暗闇に消えていく
They disappear into the darkness at the bottom of the sea
ごめんね
I'm sorry,
今まで
...until now...
気づかなかったことがあるんだけど
...there are things I hadn't realized...
こうして
...but because...
あなたが
...you...
いてくれたから今の私がいる
...were here for me, I am who I am today
過去はいらない？ そんなことはない
No need for the past? That's not true
未来は見えない？ お任せじゃない！
Can't see the future? That's not up to fate!
さよなら ありがとう
Goodbye, thank you
全て受け入れて生きていくから
Because I'll accept everything and keep on living
海の底はつまらないけど
The bottom of the sea is boring, but...
あなたのことは忘れないから
...I will never forget you
いつでも
Whenever,
どこでも
...wherever...
私らしく生きていこう
...I'll live true to myself
Tokyo Wabi-Sabi Lullaby 眠れない夜には phone time
Tokyo Wabi-Sabi Lullaby, for sleepless nights, it's phone time
Oh na-na-na-na-na-na-na ねぇ元気にしてる？ 話したいよ
Oh na-na-na-na-na-na-na, hey, how are you doing? I want to talk
寂しさをこらえて またねって君は笑ってた
Holding back your loneliness, you said "see you" with a smile
Oh na-na-na-na-na-na-na
ねぇ今年の夏 また会えるかな
Hey, will we be able to meet again this summer?
桜の花びらが咲き始める頃 会いに
Around the time the cherry blossom petals start to bloom, to see you...
やぁ久しぶりだね そんな緊張おこさないで
"Hey, it's been a while," please don't get so nervous
Tokyo Wabi-Sabi Lullaby 眠れない夜には phone time
Tokyo Wabi-Sabi Lullaby, for sleepless nights, it's phone time
Oh na-na-na-na-na-na-na ねぇ元気にしてる？
Oh na-na-na-na-na-na-na, hey, how are you doing?
会えない日が続いたら 君は笑ってくれるかな
If the days we can't meet continue, will you still smile for me?
あぁとても綺麗だ 1人で見上げた夜空に花火
Ah, so beautiful, the fireworks in the night sky I looked up at alone
Mayday blue, stream my heart
何もかも蜃気楼
Everything is a mirage
夏の女神の気まぐれね
It's the whim of the summer goddess
Steal my heart
何食わぬ顔をして
Acting as if nothing happened,
Kiss me, boy
奪って
and steal me away.
Don't go away
いつかまたなんて
Saying "see you again someday"...
I never say
唇に裏腹
Saying the opposite of what's on my lips,
残したままで
leaving it just like that.
Turn around
Myth or Treat
Your oshi's waiting in the closet tonight
No way to stop, she's dead-set on giving you a fright
Trick or treat, but now we're all out of candy
Feeling just a little sick, this chainsaw ought to come in handy
Chat is blushing...
Look at those red cheeks
I'll fix that up, drain all your blood, that's what you seek
Myth or Treat
Oh, what a cursed, diversified stream!
There's no bones about it, you'll scream
Only show you on Halloween our...
...spookier, terrifying, scary side
Oh, what a gacha toy life
Mythic witches with endless bites
Can't escape our idol-ish might
No candy in sight, so your souls will suffice
パレード パレード パレード 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! Shine on!
悔しさも愛おしさも連れておいで
Bring along your regrets and your affections
風、夢、羽、飛び立てるさ
The wind, dreams, wings... we can fly!
ささやかな祈りは光 終わりなき兆し
A humble prayer is light, an endless promise
君と飛び込んでゆく 素敵にスタートさ
I'll dive in with you, making a wonderful start
ここから
From right here...
パレード、パレード、パレード
...parade, parade, parade!
Face to face with time again
We walk once more to the end
Burn it down, burn it down
Waves can't put out my flame
Death will never write my name
Burn it down, burn it down
They say the memory of me is fading
I've heard it all before
Don't tell me everyone around is waiting
And they all say Tear it down, burn it down
And they'll all pay When I tear it down, burn it down
When the world falls through
And all is ash again
While you all pretend
If this is the end, I'll do it again
Voices rise in my head
The hands that pull at my thread
Let them drown, burn it down
Wait for wash in the tide
In the abyss is where I will hide
Let them drown, burn it down
They say the memory of me is fading
I've heard it all before
Don't tell me everyone around is waiting
And they all say, "Tear it down, burn it down"
And they'll all pay, when I tear it down, burn it down
When the world falls through and all is ash again
While you all pretend, if this is the end...
...I'll do it again
We swim against the current's aim
In dark we change as smoke returns to rain
Navigating sunken depths and all of its debris
And no more hands upon my words...
...they only speak for me
For all the ones who try to silence thunder
I'm the wave that pulls you down and under
Every day I'll stand with me...
...and I'll fight the drought of shallow seas
As ships sail winds of jealousy...
...I'll listen carefully
Let it all burn down!
As they all say
Tear it down, burn it down
And they'll all pay
When I tear it down, burn it down
When the world falls through and all is ash again
While you all pretend, if this is the end...
...I'll do it again
Hi, hello! Hello, hello, thank you. Hello!
Hi.
Um, from the very bottom of my shark heart...
...thank you.
Um, if I could borrow your ear for just...
...just a bit more time, I want to thank you again.
Thank you for...
...letting me be your shark idol for the last...
...half decade?
Five years. Wow!
Well, just about five years or so.
Um, in this time...
...I, I, I have loved performing for you...
...here, or on stage, or in my bedroom.
Any... anywhere, anywhere really.
Um, I... yeah. Wow.
Speaking... speaking of half a decade...
...when I first joined Hololive,
I had barely any experience in...
...streaming, or dancing, or singing...
...in front of people.
I couldn't even sing in front of my own mother.
Um, but...
But now... now look at me, right?
I won't lie, it was really hard to get my footing.
Um, sometimes it was terrifying.
No, a lot of the time, it was terrifying.
But spending time with you and all of the...
...incredibly talented members of Hololive...
...has been an absolute pleasure.
And I can truly say...
...a highlight in my life.
I will never forget my time here at Hololive.
I feel like I've been able to grow a lot in these past years...
...not in height or brain activity, but...
In my heart,
like, my confidence...
My confidence in myself,
I believe in myself a whole lot more now
than I did five years ago, and...
Oh, it's thanks to you!
So, thank you, everyone,
for your compassion,
your creativity,
and your dedication
to me,
your Gura.
Thank you to my Myth ladies.
We've been through
so, so much together,
and I am honored to have been able to go
on this journey with you girls.
Thank you to...
Nacho-mama,
for always working so hard
and making me so darn cute!
And thank you to my Chumbies,
for always being there for me,
for pushing me to try new games,
new songs,
new experiences.
Thank you for everything.
I-I've got a Gulf Stream current to catch.
Time to otsusame
Time to say otsusame
one last time.
Ready?
Otsusame!
The biggest!
Take care,
and be kind to yourselves,
okay?
Okay.
Good night,
and goodbye.
Goodbye, goodbye.
Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye, bye-bye!
Goodbye!
Gawr Gura がうる・ぐら 卒業ミニライブ Graduation Mini Live
Gawr Gura Graduation Mini Live